PRIYA RAJ

29th Dec 1994

#141, Kamdhenu Apt, 6th Main, Anugraha layout, Bilekahalli, Bengaluru 560076 + 91- 9972897705 | priyaandalliance@gmail.com



CAREER OBJECTIVE

A challenging position in an organization that offers me the opportunities to utilize my earned skills and abilities to the fullest, and thus, add experience in tackling intriguing challenges which will help me enhance my expertise and knowledge.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Believe is putting best effort with high efficiency.
- Believe in action-oriented working.
- Like to be a team player and quality conscious.
- Patient, Self Oriented, Energetic
- Technical: MS Excel, Power Point, Word
- Linguistic: English, Hindi, Bengali, Punjabi
- Other: Soft Skills, Interpersonal Skills, Organizing events, Convincing skills

EDUCATION

ALLIANCE UNIVERSITY - BANGALORE - MASTERS IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION Specialized in MARKETING

Internship: A SURVEY ON INITIAL QUALITY OF FIRST HAND CARS IN KARNATKA

(To find the level of awareness of four wheeler among the reasons for them using/not using the service.

To analyze customer satisfaction towards four wheeler car)

Percentage- 65.69% Year: 2014-2016

> NSHM - DURGAPUR, WEST BENGAL - BACHELORS IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

Project Undertaken – Study on Consumer Perception towards PANTALOON

Specialized in MARKETING

Percentage- 61% Year: 2011-2014

> SHAH SATNAMJI GIRLS SCHOOL - SIRSA, HARYANA- Higher Secondary School

Affiliated to C.B.S.E Board

Percentage- 68% YEAR: 2009-2011

> ST PAUL SCHOOL - MUZAFFARPUR, BIHAR Senior Secondary School

Affiliated to C.B.S.E Board

Percentage- 49% YEAR: 2008-2009

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ARTHA PROPERTIES – Deputy Manger (CRM) - December 2018- till Date

Key Result Area:

- Full Customer Life cycle management, from booking till handover.
- Preparation of the Agreement for the clients who have booked plots or the apartments.
- Complaints Management, Service Assurance & Quality Monitor.
- Banking relationship, collections and recoveries.
- Building a healthy portfolio representing quality and service.
- Managing customers queries related to Flat Purchase, Construction progress, Payment Structure, generating business from existing client etc
- Creating daily scheduled reports calling list, collection update and various other reports on need basis
- Interact with customers and make follow up calls in order to collect the amounts due.
- Follow up with Bank customers to follow up with banks for fund release against the milestone achieved.
- Constant follow up emails for those customers who are delaying agreements and loan processing
- Attending the meetings and business conferences with prospective clients
- Proper coordination with team members & various departments.
- Timely execution of apartment buyer agreements and transfers of units for all the projects.

<u>KOTAK MAHINDRA – Deputy Manger (Corporate Acquisition) - August 2016 – June 2018</u>

KEY RESULT AREAS:

- To generate business for designated branch in the assigned geography.
- Sales of Corporate Account along with other bank products to the company as a whole.
- To develop leads and get companies for liability products
- Market mapping, companies mapping, competitor mapping in the geography assigned
- Managing, sourcing and acquisitions through Branch and Sales team.
- Managing acquisition programs, driving customer/Companies referral program through branch channel
- To build and maintain strong client relationship and high level of customer service.

Awards and Recognitions: Kotak Mahindra Bank

- GPA Champion for Aug 17
- 2nd Runner UP YTD Performance Sep-17
- GPA Performer Dec 2017
- 1st Performer in CORE Performance Jan- 2018.

<u>STERLING HOLIDAYS – Senior Executive - Jan 2016 – July 2016</u>

KEY RESULT AREAS

- To build and maintain strong client relationships by effectively handling objections and resolve member/customer conflicts thus building customer trust.
- To build & mp; maintain strong relationships with channel partners to achieve sales targets.
- To identify potential customers, create and close new business opportunities in line with the strategic direction of the company.
- To prepare pre-sales proposals for prospective clients.
- To make inspiring sales presentations to the prospective clients by creating a dream.
- Regular liaison with telemarketing and member relations department to achieve stretched targets in a result-focused environment.
- To build and maintain strong client relationship and high level of customer service.
- To keep abreast with the organization's products and services and to crack profitable deals and referrals to achieve sales targets.

EXTRA CURRICULAR

- Awarded as 2nd position in Basketball in sports day in college in 2014
- Organizer of different types of events in school, NCC, Active volunteer in HELP AGE INDIA, and different types of Social activities
- Participated in Blood Donation camps
- Participated Social Activities like Planting trees, Donating food and clothes to poor children
- Natural Photography
- Swimming/Travelling